<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Wings to fly</title>
    <link>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Wings to fly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:39:31 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Job Search Sites in 2020 [For Every Industry]</title>
      <link>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/job-searching-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:39:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/job-searching-websites/</guid>
      <description>Best Job Search Sites in 2020 These job boards have something for everyone.
Regardless of your profession or field, you’re probably going to find something that’s relevant for you.
Indeed Indeed is one of the most popular job boards on the internet - you’ve probably heard of it.
What makes it so popular is that all you have to do is type in your job title keywords and your location on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Sites For Free Online Education</title>
      <link>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/online-websites-to-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:23:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/online-websites-to-learn/</guid>
      <description>The 10 best sites for free online education   Coursera   Coursera.org is one of the leading providers of MOOCs – massive open online courses. It is a website that partners with universities and organizations around the world to bring a wide variety of topics and perspectives to one searchable database. This gives the site an extremely wide range of in-depth courses. Some Coursera courses provide certificates of completion to recognize that you passed the class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus (COVID-19): Home Care &amp; Precautions</title>
      <link>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/covid-precautions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:09:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wingstofly.vercel.app/news/covid-precautions/</guid>
      <description>Coronavirus (COVID-19): Home Care &amp;amp; Precautions Doctors might recommend home care if someone in your family:
 has coronavirus (COVID-19) was tested for COVID-19 and is waiting for the results has flu symptoms (like a fever, cough, and sore throat)  Anyone who is sick — even if they don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure they have coronavirus (COVID-19) — should stay home unless they need medical care. This helps prevent the illness from spreading to other people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>